

Date of birth: 26/05/89

- San Jose, Costa Rica
- rhhaiyin@gmail.com
- ☐ medulla.tech

SKILLS SUMMARY

- •••• HTML
- •••• CSS
- •••• Javascript
- •••• Photoshop & Dreamweaver
- •••• Web development
- ••• Image based email

JOI YAN R. HUANG

PERSONAL PROFILE

I'm an e-mail marketing deployment specialist working at Cheetah Digital for over 3 years now. I've been teaching myself to program in Javascript and front-end web development. My experience at this job has let me to learn about e-mail and coding best practices which I apply in my day to day tasks. I've also learned how to better work with team mates. I have a computer science and business administration background. I'm ready to take on a new venture by becoming a full time coder and begin to apply the skills I've acquired over the years.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Deployment Specialist

Cheetah Digital | March 2018 - present

- Set up of e-mail marketing campaigns from html to the different deployment stages.
- Deploying dynamic content for e-mail.
- Coding of HTML and styling content for client's promotional e-mails.
- Account documentation and guidelines.
- Task Management.

Roku Technical Support | English/French

Concentrix | Dec 2013 - Oct 2016

- Customer handling skills
- Troubleshooting device and communicating with users of different cultural backgrounds

LANGUAGES

English - Proficient
Native Spanish
French - Intermediate level

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Bachillerato en Administración de Empresas

Universidad Estatal a Distancia | Jan 2018 - Present

Diplomado en Informatica

Universidad Estatal a Distancia | Jan 2019 - Present